Sara-Jane Gibbs

UX Designer

Profile

I am a UX designer who aspires to create engaging products that ultimately help people in their day to day life.

My previous role was in digital production at Arcadia Group. Spanning 7 years I worked directly on the delivery of digital products for Evans, most recently, the desktop and mobile website relaunches. This experience has given me knowledge of digital capabilities and experience working closely with designers, web developers and stakeholders.

Experience

UXDI Teaching Assistant

General Assembly / June 2017 - Present

I am currently working as a teaching assistant for the UX Design Immersive course. Having completed the course in April, I am able to offer valuable support and advice to students.

UX Designer

O2 World Chat / May 2017

Working in a team, our goal was to redesign how users discover and engage with the sharing functionality within the iOS app. In a two week sprint, we focused on user research, heuristic analysis, information architecture, creating wireframes, prototyping, testing and iterating our designs. We were then able to deliver high-fidelity designs, a revised site map and final stakeholder presentation.

UX Designer

Generation Success / April 2017

Working in a team, in a two week sprint, our goal was to redesign Generation Success' website. In this sprint, through user research, information architecture, wireframing, prototyping and testing we produced a high-fidelity responsive website design, design specification, final stakeholder presentation and wider site recommendations.

UX Designer

General Assembly / February 2017 - April 2017

A 10 week, full time immersive course learning and practising the UX design process. Throughout the course I worked on projects which covered user research, interaction and interface design, prototyping and testing, and working with clients.

Projects:

Science Museum App:

Delivery of high-fidelity wireframes for an app that enhances the visitors experience. Working in a team of four, in a two week sprint, through user research, sketching and wireframing, prototyping and testing, we produced an engaging app that allows visitors to plan their visit and navigate around the museum with use of an interactive map.

Contact

London

07837950449

sarajanegibbs@gmail.com

sarajanegibbs.co.uk

linkedin.com/in/sarajanegibbs

Key Skills

User Research

User Flows

User Journeys

Task Analysis

Affinity Map

Information Architecture

Wireframing

Prototyping

Interaction Design

Usability Testing

Presentations

Agile Methodologies

Teamwork

Self Motivation

Communication

Software

Sketch

Omnigraffle

Marvel

Invision

JIRA

Photoshop

HTML & CSS

Keynote

Sara-Jane Gibbs

UX Designer

Experience Continued

Ecommerce Website:

Delivery of desktop wireframes for a new ecommerce website. Working individually, I produced wireframes for a product list page, product detail page and checkout flow.

Online Production Coordinator

Evans - Arcadia / May 2014 - February 2017

Key Responsibilities:

- Coordinated daily CMS builds of website content on desktop, mobile and apps.
- Management of two Production Assistants; responsible for their training and development.
- Worked closely with marketing and design teams to ensure that content was delivered on time.
- Along with Production Manager, helped develop website.
- Worked closely with website development team to implement new site functionality.
- Worked with third parties to carry out Multivariate and A/B Testing

Key Achievements:

- Managed the implementation and launch of a new mobile platform for Evans. Working closely with development teams and Project Managers.
- Managed the relaunch of the desktop website, transferring data from one programme to another and thoroughly testing the customer experience.

Online Production Assistant

Wallis - Arcadia / July 2010 - May 2014

Key Responsibilities:

- Management of online catalogue; creating and updating categories, uploading product and setting up promotions on a daily basis.
- Worked alongside the Marketing team to carry out keyword research for each season. From this research, I was responsible for writing on-site content and meta-data and making sure that the website was optimised.
- Involved in the implementation of iPads in selected stores, training store staff on how to help customers place orders online.

Key Achievements:

• As part of a team, I was involved with the launch of iOS and Android apps, this included thorough testing of the apps and working with a third party.

Education

UXDI Course

General Assembly / February -April 2017

B.A Media Studies

De Montfort University / 2007 - 2010

Interests

Exploring new countries and trying new and exciting food.

I love music and finding new artists to listen to, when I hear an album I really like, I'll play it on repeat for weeks.

Looking through cookbooks and trying new recipes.

Exploring London. I have lived here all my life, but there is constantly more and more to see and do. It is such a great city to live in.